In front of me here is Iman Gadzhi.
Whether you're a believer in his courses
or his
entrepreneurial skills,
there's one thing we can't deny.
His channel performs incredibly well.
I have it on good authority
that he has a rather large team of very
intelligent,
smart people,
that every single thing he does
is incredibly strategic.
And if we go onto his videos,
with a vidIQ plugin, we can see
that some videos
perform better than others. And down here,
there is an outlier, 7.9
times better than any of his other videos.
So for it to be an outlier on his channel,
I thought surely this can be an outlier
on my channel. And
if you look across all of my videos here,
you can see
7.5 times. And the glasses,
where he had glasses on in his.
I stole his packaging. But it gets worse.
I also stole some other things. Oh,
it's actually quite nice.
You get a bit used to them
when they're on.
His title,
"Laziest Way to Make Money in 2025
($100 a Day) " .My title,
($350 a Day) " .
Again, if we go back to RevTrack,
nearly $13,000 of attributed
direct sales,
let alone any of the sales and clicks
that have gone through lead
magnets after that point. Two
and a half thousand clicks.
Spoke about that in the last video.
After seeing an outlier on a channel like
Iman's, I would actually be almost stupid
to not try and mimic it
and make it my own.
But this is where I become a dirty piece
of shit. I didn't watch his video.
I went down to the transcript.
I copied it.
I went to ChatGPT,
"Give me the sentiment
and lessons of this video." Then when I
went through what this
was telling me about the sentiment
and the core thesis,
I realized that his video
and my skill sets
are vastly differently aligned.
So I then copied this,
put it into a document,
and deleted all the parts out that I
couldn't really give you any advice on.
You'd be better getting it from Iman.
And then actually started putting things
in there that could potentially benefit
you. I know the packaging
is going to work,
but I don't want to talk about AI.
I don't want to talk about pre-sales.
I don't want to talk about this.
And I can even ask it here to give me
chapters that I could use for my own
video.
This just gave me a template
that I could build upon.
And if you watch our videos,
you'll know they're vastly different.
But this is where things get snakey to the
fourth degree.
There's 1,190 comments on this.
So I copied them all.
I don't just want to know what's said in
the video.
I want to know what people
are saying about the video,
because this could have an
impact on how I start
and position my video.
This is over 1,000 pieces of feedback to a
video that I'm about to
steal.
The correct term we're trying to use
is emulate. We are emulating.
We are taking inspiration from something.
This may seem sinister, but
when there's a new Batman coming out with
the guy
from Twilight, no one's thinking,
"I can't believe there's another
Batman. You stole it."
But then even the one with Christian Bale
was done off the
one with George Clooney, which
was done off the one with the other guy.
Same as Spider-Man.
We've got so many Spider-Mans.
There's three of them in the same one.
As I learnt from Ed Lawrence,
most films have got the same storyline.
Finding Nemo and Taken have got the same
storyline. No one's kicking off.
My God, that's a lot of comments.
We'll get to this bit here, okay? Cool.
We're going to copy that.
Now tell me the generalized feedback from
the
comments posted in all the comments.
Now, the sentiment I got
when I put this into ChatGPT before
was people were
saying that they were grateful
that this wasn't a video just about
getting rich.
This was a video about providing for your
families.
It was a video about looking after loved
ones.
I appreciate there
are a lot of bellends online all talking
about making money.
I just want to make one thing clear.
I'm making these videos not so you can get
rich.
This is about providing for your families,
escaping financial stress, and
just having more confidence within
whatever it is you want to do without
burning
out.
And it was about making more confidence
without burning out. How do I know?
Because I've just gone
and had a little look here.
And to preface my entire video,
I came out with the feedback
that I got from Iman's comments.
And you can see down here all the
different
variations of thumbnails
which I used to test whether
or not having the
money there or didn't would perform
better.
1,100 subscribers,
6,000 hours of watch time.
What I'm saying is,
not so much you need to steal good ideas.
What I'm saying is, it
is very foolish for you to not
emulate and take inspiration from things
that are doing well because every single
thing you see around you that's performing
well isn't original.
All the businesses I have
are coined from ideas of other things
that I studied in
and worked within.
And it's not just our ability to be good
at what we do as a job,
it's our ability to see trends,
to see things that are performing, to use
tools to spot outliers.
Even MrBeast's videos have
sometimes been copied from concepts of
other creators.
If you do not emulate successful
strategies
and implement them into your own content
and social
media,
you quite simply will get left behind.
And if we type in that title,
"The Laziest Way to Make Money",
"The Laziest Way to
Make Money with AI",
"The Laziest Way to Make Money in 2025",
"The Laziest Way to
Make Money with AI", Dan Martell,
"How to Actually Make Money in 2025".
He said $500 a day.
"The Laziest Ways to Make Money with AI".
I'm not bitter.
"Laziest Ways to Make Money Online in 2025
($100 a Day) " .
I'm not bitter about these people because
they're doing what I did.
And the person that I copied probably
copied someone else.
This is the game where stealing ideas
and inspiration are pretty much the same
thing. Who knows?
Maybe even this video
was stolen from another one that I'd seen.
Hope that video's got your brain thinking,
and you're going to go out onto the
internet and look for some good ideas
that you can be emulated by.
There's going to be links in the
description to the products that I do,
but if not,
there's a video right here
that you can jump into
that YouTube's recommended.
And if you watch that,
you might love it just as much as this
one. Bye-bye.